Hi, my name is Patrick Nussbaumer and I'll be your instructor for this course.
嗨 我是 Patrick Nussbaumer 我是这门课程的指导老师
I work for Alteryx, a leader in self-service data analytics.
我为 Alteryx 工作 这是一家在自助数据分析领域具有领导地位的公司
And have worked with data acquisition and analysis for over 20 years.
我从事数据采集和分析的工作已经超过20年了
In this course,
在这门课程中
we'll be learning how to approach a business problem using analytics.
我们将会学习如何用分析来解决一个商业问题
Let's talk about an example that we'll reference throughout this course.
让我们来讨论一个在课程中将会被反复提及的例子
Let's consider this scenario.
让我们来考虑如下的情况
You recently joined a multinational firm that provides automated robots
你最近加入了一个提供自动机器人的跨国公司
that vacuum office spaces.
这些机器人是用来清洁办公空间的
For larger office spaces, more robots are needed,
工作空间越大就需要越多的机器人
and the software configuration to run the robots becomes more complex.
并且用于驱动这些机器人的软件设置也变得更加复杂
To support your clients, you have a help desk that manages support tickets.
为了帮助你的客户 你有一个用来管理工单的服务台
Due to the nature of the business, it's critical that the help desk is staffed
因为这个公司的特性 服务台上一直有工作人员
properly to ensure smooth operation of the army of cleaning robots.
来保证一大群清扫机器人顺畅运行非常重要
Your manager has tasked you with the following business problem.
你的经理用如下的商业问题来考验你
We're onboarding a new client next month as part of a very large deal.
下个月我们将与一位新客户开展一项大型交易
It's critical that we support them with our excellent service levels.
我们要以优质的服务水平为他们提供支持
I need to know how many tickets per week on average we can expect from this
我需要知道平均每周这位客人会提交多少工单
client so we can ensure we have enough help desk resources in place.
以确保帮助台有足够的资源
But before we attempt to solve this problem, we need to spend some time
不过在我们试图解决这个问题之前
discussing how to approach business problems with analytics and
我们需要花一些时间讨论 如何用分析方法和预测模型
predictive models.
来解决商业问题
First, we're going to discuss a framework for
第一 我们要来讨论一个
solving analytical problems.
解决分析性问题的框架
Second, we'll talk about non-predictive data analysis.
第二 我们要讨论非预测性数据分析
And third, we'll return to our business problem and
第三 我们将回归我们的商业问题
talk about predictive analysis, which will lead us to review a process for
并且讨论预测性分析 预测性分析将带领我们检视
selecting the right predictive model.
选择合适预测模型的过程
And lastly, we're going to discuss linear regressions, which is
最后 我们将讨论线性回归
the technique we'll use to solve our support ticket business problem.
我们将用线性回归来解决我们的商业问题
All right, let's get going.
好的 让我们开始吧